<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">EnjayInterviewApp</string>

    <string name="client_ID">464487550920-15oebpan5hh7kg721fus0muqvu8qvraj.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>

    <string name="facebook_app_id">498821489001387</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb498821489001387</string>
    <string name="facebook_client_token">8e2ccf4a032072fe9af6d5e6b539ce07</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="Open">open</string>
    <string name="Close">close</string>

    <string name="common_interview_question">COMMON INTERVIEW QUESTION</string>

    <string name="number1">How to Answer :-\n\nTo answer, walk them through our background, starting at how we began our career or our current line of work.\n
Take them through key accomplishments,key career moves we’ve made, and end by sharing what we’re looking to do next in our career and why we’re job hunting.\n
Good answer sample :-\n
“I started my career in Marketing after graduating with a Business degree in 2011.\n
I’ve spent my entire career at Google, receiving 3 promotions and 4 awards for outstanding performance.\n
I’m looking to join a smaller company now, and take on more leadership and project management.”</string>

    <string name="number2">How to Answer :-\n\nThis is one of the simplest question and answer scenarios in any interview, but that doesn’t mean it can’t ruin our chances at the job if we answer incorrectly.\n
Good answer sample :-\n
“I saw the job posted on a website, and the position seemed interesting so I wanted to learn more”\n
“I found the position while looking for jobs online”\n
“Your company was recommended to me by somebody I worked with in a previous job and had heard good things about your organization”\n
“I heard about it from a friend”</string>

    <string name="number3">How to Answer :-\n\nWe need to sound like we want the RIGHT job and that we’re being picky.Companies want the best performers, and the best performers are picky in their job hunt.\n
Stay away from negatives and complaints too. Do not bad-mouth our current company or boss.\n
Focus on the positives of the company we’re interviewing with.\n
Good answer sample :-\n
“I’ve heard great things about the work environment here from a few colleagues.And when I saw this job posting, it seemed to match my skills very closely. For example, I saw on the job description that you need somebody who’s an expert in mySQL programming.\n
This is what I focused on in both of my previous positions, and was even the focus of my academic work before graduating university. I consider myself an expert in mySQL and it’s a skill I hope to continue specializing in.”\n
“Since beginning my career, I’ve wanted to work for a larger organization in this industry, and I know you’re one of the leaders in this space.\n
I’m very interested in your services, especially the mobile applications you’re building recently,so I’d be excited to come here and grow my skills with an organization like yours.”</string>

    <string name="number4">How to Answer :-\n\nTry to talk about them and how we’ll help them. What will be better for them if they hire us?\n
What will we improve for them?\n
And show we’ve done our research. Make it clear that we know what this position involves, and we’re ready to perform the tasks.\n
Good answer sample :-\n
“I read on the job description that you’re looking for someone with experience in software programming. I’ve done that for 3 years and can immediately help you accomplish software programming”.</string>

    <string name="number5">How to Answer :-\n\nIf we chose to leave on our own terms, stay positive and focus on what we wanted to gain from the decision, rather than bad-mouthing or focusing on negatives we wanted to avoid.\n
Good answer sample :-\n
“I was hired for a project management role, but over time that changed and I was no longer being given the opportunity to do the work I was interested in.\n
I left to pursue an opportunity that I felt was more aligned with what I’ve chosen to focus on in my career.”</string>

    <string name="number6">How to Answer :-\n\nAnswer it well and it’s one of the best ways we can show off our skills and show that we stand out among other candidates.\n
Choose 1 to 3 attributes we want to mention (depending on whether the question asks for one strength or multiple) and cap it there.\n
We’ll want to think strategically about what skills will position us as qualified for the job and a good fit for the company.\n
Does the position require client interaction? Communication and relationship building makes sense.\n
Or if the environment is fast paced and constantly evolving our ability to multitask, adapt, and learn quickly would be good to highlight.\n
Good answer sample :-\n
“I think some of my greatest strengths are my communication skills and willingness to take initiative.\n
During my last internship, when I was helping to manage several social media accounts, I made sure that everyone on the team was on the same page and knew what our messaging strategy was by taking the initiative to send out a weekly email to keep the team up to date and to seek feedback.\n
This ended up being so helpful that the weekly social media update was incorporated into a full-time staff member’s responsibilities.”</string>

    <string name="number7">How to Answer :-\n\nFocus on a specific work-related challenge and talk about how we overcame obstacles, used it as a learning experience, used the resources around us (including people/colleagues if applicable),and ended up with a positive result! \n
That’s how to answer this interview question. Keep it work related, not personal.\n
Good answer sample :-\n
“In my last job, we were facing a tough deadline and my boss was out for the day. Our client was expecting a project to be delivered by 5PM, but we were far behind schedule. \n
I took the lead on the project, delegated tasks to the four other team members in a way that I thought would utilize everyone’s strengths best.And then I re-organized my own personal tasks so I could dedicate my entire day to contributing to this project as well.\n
The project was a success and we delivered the work on-time. I went on to lead more projects after that, and used what I learned to be a better project manager.”
    </string>

    <string name="number8">How to Answer :-\n\nUnfortunately this question is left off of many lists of job interview questions and answers examples.\n
But it’s extremely important and the wrong answer here can cost us thousands of dollars in the negotiation later on.\n
Stand our ground and tell them we don’t have a number in mind yet, or aren’t sure.\n
Good answer sample :- \n
“Right now I’m focused on finding a job that’s the right fit for my career.\n
Once I’ve done that, I’m willing to consider an offer you feel is fair, but I do not have a specific number in mind yet, and my priority is to find a position that’s a great fit for me.”</string>

    <string name="number9">How to Answer :-\n\nThis is very similar to the question: “Why did you apply for this position?”\n
Show them that we know what that their job involves (at least as much as we could learn from the job description and company website), and that we’re excited to be interviewing for this position.\n
Good answer sample :-\n
“I’ve been actively searching for jobs since graduating with my Nursing degree.\n
I’m interested in intensive care and emergency medicine and I’ve seen your hospital mentioned as having one of the best ER’s in the region.\n
I thought the job description matched up well with my background, and saw some of my personal strengths mentioned, like multitasking and being able to thrive in a fast paced environment,so I’d love to begin my career here.”</string>

    <string name="number10" tools:ignore="StringEscaping,TypographyEllipsis">How to Answer :-\n\nCareer counselors like to think about good jobs as the intersection of our skills, interests, and values.\n
That’s a good way for us to approach it as well. Talking about our skills will give us an opportunity to sell them a bit—after all, it is an interview\n
Our interests will show our investment, and our values can help illustrate our fit with the company.\n
Good answer sample :-\n
"I’ve thought about this before, and I know I would want to keep honing my skills in … as well as learn more about… ."\n
"In terms of job content, I’m interested in work that involves … and ... . I’ve been curious about things like this ever since ..., so I would definitely want that to be part of my dream job."\n
"Based on my skills and interests, in my dream job, I would want to ... as related to ..., ideally in a company where I could ... and .... These are both really important to me, and I’m excited to see that they seem to be equally important to this company."</string>

    <string name="number11">How to Answer :-\n\nIf we chose to leave on our own terms, stay positive and focus on what we wanted to gain from the decision, rather than bad-mouthing or focusing on negatives we wanted to avoid.\n
Good answer sample :-\n
“I left for an opportunity to advance my career.”\n
“My department brought in a new manager and I felt it was the right time to leave.”\n
“I was hired for a certain role, but over time that changed and I was no longer being given the opportunity to do the work I was interested in.”\n
“I didn’t feel there was an opportunity to grow or advance further in that role so I decided a change would best for my career.”\n
“I had been with the organization for a number of years and wanted to experience a new environment to continue growing.”</string>

    <string name="number12">How to Answer :-\n\nHiring managers are curious about what other companies we’re interviewing with for a few reasons.\n
They might want to scope out the competition, see how serious we are about the industry, or even gauge their likelihood of landing such a star candidate.\n
Good answer sample :-\n
If we’re Interviewing for Competitors:\n
"I do have a couple of interviews coming up soon with … for senior marketing positions.\n
But I can tell you that, based on what I know, this position has exactly the kinds of challenges\n
I’m looking for in my next role."\n\n
If we’re Interviewing in Other Industries :-\n
"I’m interviewing with a few companies for a range of positions, but they all come down to delivering an excellent customer experience.\n
I wanted to keep an open mind about how to best achieve that goal, but so far it seems that this role will really allow me to focus all of my energy on customer experience and retention, which I find very appealing."\n
If we’re Not Interviewing Anywhere Else :-\n
"I’m still pretty early in my job search. I’ve applied to a number of opportunities that will allow me to use my skills in data visualization to help educate clients, but this position is most exciting to me.\n
In fact, I think this position is a particularly good fit for my skill set because I can leverage my significant experience working with complicated data sets."</string>

    <string name="number13">How to Answer :-\n\nWe never want to say we struggle working with others, or we’re bad at resolving disagreements,or taking direction from a manager, etc. Those things will get us rejected in the interview.\n
So pick a specific skill, but pick something that won’t severely impact our ability to do this job.\n
Good answer sample :-\n
“I’m not particularly strong in social media marketing. For the first few years of my career, I focused entirely on email marketing.\n
That’s still what I specialize in, which is why I applied for your Email Marketing Manager job.\n
But I’ve realized it’s also helpful to understand the principles of social media marketing because some of the strategies that work there also work well in email.\n
So I’ve started spending a couple hours a week of my own time studying and learning this new area, and it’s helped me a lot.”</string>

    <string name="number14" tools:ignore="StringEscaping">How to Answer :-\n\nIdeally one that is similar to the environment of the company we are applying to. Be specific.\n
Although most places have a section on their sites devoted to explaining culture, they tend to be filled with phrases like “dedicated to customer satisfaction” and “we encourage our employees to grow.” That tells us a whole lot of nothing.</string>

    <string name="number15">How to Answer :-\n\nBrainstorm a few more questions that could potentially come up based on the position we’re applying for and our particular situation.\n
For example, say we tell that story about standing up to the director of marketing when asked to talk about conflict with a previous supervisor.\n
We eloquently move through the story about how we shared our hesitation about the new marketing campaign to no avail, but once the initial numbers came in, it was clear that we were right.\n
We triumphantly showed the performance to the director, and she agreed to scrap the campaign.\n
Good answer sample :-\n
“I learned early on in my professional career that it’s fine to disagree if you can back up your hunches with data.”\n
“In short, it’s not that I’m an amazing multitasker; I just set and review my priorities frequently.”
</string>

    <string name="number16">How to Answer :-\n\nPick a work-related goal of where we’d like to be five years from now, and make sure it’s slightly challenging or ambitious-sounding.\n
And make sure to share a goal that is related to the type of job we’re interviewing for.\n
We want to sound like the experience we’ll gain in this job fits our long-term goals.\n
Good answer sample :-\n
“I’m glad you asked. In five years I see myself taking on more responsibilities, either through management or higher level individual contributions.\n
I am not sure which path will make sense to pursue, but I know my goal right now is to build a strong foundation and gain valuable experience so that I’ll have a successful future in this industry.”
</string>

    <string name="number17" tools:ignore="StringEscaping">How to Answer :-\n\nHave a target audience, and speak directly to it. It is super important for any job seeker.\n
We’re not going to be able to just list out our job history and expect a financial services hiring manager to instantly deduce what we have to offer.\n
Instead, we will need to angle all of our messaging in a way that makes it obvious what we’re trying to achieve, and why we’re heading in that direction.\n
A good rule of thumb is that, if we’re worried how a certain position or experience is going to be perceived on our resume, there’s a good chance that someone is going to make the exact conclusion we don’t want them to make.\n
That said, we should plan to go on the offense and manage the message.\n
For instance, say the moves we’ve made along the way make we look, at least on paper, like a bit of a job hopper.\n
It’s best to add a quick statement in each section of our resume that briefly explains the jump.\n
Think through how we’re going to present our choices and career path to a potential employer,present them briefly and confidently, and then refocus the discussion on our commitment to this role and what we can walk through that company’s doors and deliver.\n
Good answer sample :-\n
“Following a family relocation to Dallas…” (makes the job switch obvious) or “After a significant corporate restructure…” (makes it clear that our job was axed).
</string>

    <string name="number18">How to Answer :-\n\nThis is a common interview question that employers ask to see if we’re able to learn from mistakes and bounce back when things don’t go our way.\n
Ideally, talk about how we used that lesson to get a different outcome next time we were presented with a similar challenge (e.g. how we turned a past failure into a future success).\n
Good answer sample :-\n
“In my most recent position, I had recently been promoted to Supervisor, and was managing the department on my own right before the department closed.\n
An employee was acting out and I confronted him in front of everybody. It made the situation worse and caused a lot of distraction for every employee on the floor.\n
I failed to lead properly in this situation, and spoke to my manager the next day to discuss what I could have done differently.\n
We both agreed that I should have handled this in-private with the employee, by asking them to step inside my office with me.\n
If I had done this instead of reacting the way I did, the situation would have turned out much better.\n
From that point onward, I am always conscious of whether a discussion with a team member should occur in public or behind closed doors, and it made me a better leader.”</string>

    <string name="number19">This is our chance to use the words of others to talk about our own positive traits.\n
Good answer sample :-\n
"Actually, in my most recent performance review in May, my direct supervisor described me as someone who takes initiative and doesn’t shy away from hard problems./n
My role involves a lot of on-site implementation, and when things go wrong, it’s usually up to me to fix it.\n
Rather than punting the problem back to the team, I always try to do what I can first. I know she appreciates that about me."\n
"One thing I’ve noticed is that I’m always the one people turn to for recommendations on how to handle a new event or program—the latest fundraiser that I just told you about would be one.\n
I have a lot of institutional knowledge, which helps, but I think the reason people come to me is because I work through what a new program might look like very methodically.\n
If you were to ask my colleagues, I’m confident they’d describe me as logical, organized, and meticulous."\n
"I don’t want to speak for anyone else, but I’m pretty confident my colleagues would describe me as thoughtful I’m the one in the office who remembers everyone’s birthdays—and hard-working,since I never leave my office until it’s been dark out for a couple of hours.\n
My boss in particular would say I’m very knowledgeable about audience development it’s why I kept taking on more and more responsibilities in that domain."
</string>

    <string name="number20" tools:ignore="StringEscaping">A great approach is to talk through our go-to stress-reduction tactics (making the world is greatest to-do list, stopping to take 10 deep breaths), and then share an example of a stressful situation you navigated with ease.\n
The thing people assume about these questions is that they’re all about the story. And it is a critical component.\n
But even if our story isn’t exactly what the interview question asked for, if it’s framed well and we go the extra mile to tell the interviewer what he or she should take away from it, we’ll actually end up making a stronger impression.\n
So, don’t stress too much about having the perfect stories lined up or the exact relevant experience. Instead, focus on the messages we’re trying to communicate to the hiring manager, and back them up with the stories that we have.</string>

    <string name="number21">No matter what role we’re interviewing for (engineering, sales, marketing) we should always use the product before our first interview (and ideally, a few times).\n
If hired, our goal will be to create value for the people who use that product, and being a user ourself is the first step.\n
Doing this will also help us determine whether we can be passionate about the company and product as well as convey that passion to our interviewer.\n
Now that we’re familiar with the product, be ready with ideas for how we’d like to improve it in our role.\n
What new features would we be most excited to build?\n
How would we engage users (or re-engage existing ones)?\n
How could the company increase conversions?\n
How could customer service be improved?\n
When we’re interviewing with a start-up, our goal is to ensure that the job is a great fit for us, and to convey that to our interviewer as well.\n
When we do, we’ll be in a better position to negotiate our offer and get started once we accept it—full of ideas on ways to hit the ground running.</string>

    <string name="number22">If someone asks about our hobbies outside of work, it’s totally OK to open up and share what really makes we tick.\n
(Do keep it semi-professional, though: Saying we like to have a few beers at the local hot spot on Saturday night is fine. Telling them that Monday is usually a rough day for us because we’re always hungover is not.)\n
It goes without saying that we should find out everything we can about our potential place of employment ahead of time.\n
Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, and the company’s website and blog all provide us with information that will help we go to a job interview confident and prepared.\n
Before we go, try to find out who we’ll be meeting with, whether it’s an HR representative, our would-be boss, or the CEO.\n
Why? our interview answers and conversation topics should vary based on the person we are speaking with, and by knowing who we will be talking to, we can spend time thinking through how we might connect with each of these people
    </string>

    <string name="number23">\nI think one of my greatest strengths is learning things quickly and staying positive. An example could be in recent years, my professor told me to come up with a new idea and that field was totally new for me. Every time I came up with an idea, either it was either already solved or not feasible at my personal level. So my Idea was not falling into place but by continuing to read and going through the literature survey and keeping myself motivated, I come up with an idea which is new and implementable at my level.\n
    </string>

    <string name="number24">Unfortunately this question is left off of many lists of job interview questions and answers samples.\n
But it’s extremely important, and the wrong answer here can cost us thousands of dollars in the negotiation later on.\n
They do not know if we’re any good or if they even want to hire us.\n
So we can’t command a high salary right now. If we go too low with our price, they’ll hold us to it later.\n
Go too high? We’ll scare them off before they even know what we’re worth!\n
Stand our ground and tell them we don’t have a number in mind yet, or aren’t sure.\n
Good answer sample :-\n
“Right now I’m focused on finding a job that’s the right fit for my career.\n
Once I’ve done that, I’m willing to consider an offer you feel is fair, but I do not have a specific number in mind yet, and my priority is to find a position that’s a great fit for me.”
</string>

    <string name="number25">Do not ask about salary, benefits, time off, or anything that isn’t related to the work.\n
Wait for them to bring it up, or until we know they want to offer us the position.\n
If we don’t ask good questions to each person we speak with, we are very unlikely to get hired.\n
Good answer sample :-\n
“Yes, I have a couple of questions actually. The first thing I wanted to ask: is this a newly-created position, or did somebody hold this role in the past? And if so, what did that person go on to do after this position?”</string>


    //android

    <string name="android1">\nAndroid is an open-sourced operating system that is used on mobile devices, such as mobiles and tablets. The Android application executes within its own process and its own instance of Dalvik Virtual Machine(DVM) or Android RunTime(ART).\n
    </string>

    <string name="android2">\nJava and Kotlin\n
    </string>

    <string name="android3">\nActivity in java is a single screen that represents GUI(Graphical User Interface) with which users can interact in order to do something like dial the phone, view email, etc.\n
For example, the Facebook start page where you enter your email/phone number and password to log in acts as an activity\n
    </string>

    <string name="android4">\nService is an application component that facilitates an application to run in the background in order to perform long-running operations without user interaction. A service can run continuously in the background even if the application is closed or even after the user switches to another application.\n
    </string>

    <string name="android5">\nThe core building blocks of Android are:\n\n
1. Activity\n
2. View\n
3. Intent\n
4. Service\n
5. Content Provider\n
6. Fragment etc.\n
    </string>

    <string name="android6">\nThere are 7 life-cycle methods of activity. They are as follows:\n\n
1. onCreate()\n
2. onStart()\n
3. onResume()\n
4. onPause()\n
5. onStop()\n
6. onRestart()\n
7. onDestroy()\n
    </string>

    <string name="android7">\nIt is a kind of message or information that is passed to the components. It is used to launch an activity, display a web page, send SMS, send email, etc. There are two types of intents in android:\n\n
1. Implicit Intent\n
2. Explicit Intent\n
    </string>

    //ios

    <string name="ios1">\nARC (Automatic Reference Counting) is a compiler-level feature that defines the process of managing the lifetime of objects in objective-C.\n
    </string>

    <string name="ios2">\nThe bundle ID is used for both OS X apps and iOS.  It uniquely defines every iOS application. A bundle identifier can recognize any update to your app.\n
    </string>

    <string name="ios3">\nThere are four data types which are as follows:\n
1. Bool\n
2. CGfloat\n
3. NSintegar\n
4. NSstring\n
    </string>

    <string name="ios4">\nIt is used for building software codes to run on iOS for the iPad and iPhone. Cocoa Touch is written in the objective-C language and has a different set of graphical control elements to Cocoa.\n
    </string>

    <string name="ios5">\nThe methods to achieve concurrency are:\n
1. Dispatch queues\n
2. Threads\n
3. Operation Queues\n
    </string>

    <string name="ios6">\nIt is said when it is not launched or gets terminated by the system while running.\n
    </string>

    //web

    <string name="web1">\nA beginner web developer is expected to have a fundamental knowledge of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and other aspects like jQuery, SQL, and some other scripting languages. An experienced web developer is expected to have all the given aspects and great knowledge of design patterns.\n
</string>

    <string name="web2">\nThe advantages are:\n
1. Data compression through HTTP headers.\n
2. Ease of logical server push technology.\n
3. Prioritizing a request.\n
4. Page element loading through TCP connection.\n
    </string>

    <string name="web3">\nHTML stands for Hyper Text Markup Language. It is a language of World Wide Web. It is a standard text formatting language which is used to create and display pages on the Web. It makes the text more interactive and dynamic. It can turn text into images, tables, links.\n
    </string>

    <string name="web4">\nHTML tags are composed of three things: an opening tag, content and ending tag. Some tags are unclosed tags.\n
HTML documents contain two things :\n
1. content\n
2. tags\n
When a web browser reads an HTML document, the browser reads it from top to bottom and left to right. HTML tags are used to create HTML documents and render their properties. Each HTML tags have different properties.\n
    </string>

    <string name="web5">\nCSS stands for Cascading Style Sheet. It is a popular styling language which is used with HTML to design websites. It can also be used with any XML documents including plain XML, SVG, and XUL.\n
    </string>

    <string name="web6">\nSGML (Standard Generalized Markup Language) is the origin of CSS. It is a language that defines markup languages.\n
    </string>

</resources>